[
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 5 + 5 \u00d7 10?",
      "correctAnswer": "55",
      "options": [
        "60",
        "57",
        "55",
        "53"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 2 + 3 \u00d7 8?",
      "correctAnswer": "26",
      "options": [
        "24",
        "31",
        "28",
        "26"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 13 + 1 \u00d7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "14",
      "options": [
        "12",
        "16",
        "14",
        "19"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 11 + 5 \u00d7 6?",
      "correctAnswer": "41",
      "options": [
        "41",
        "46",
        "39",
        "43"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 11 + 1 \u00d7 7?",
      "correctAnswer": "18",
      "options": [
        "23",
        "18",
        "20",
        "16"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 19 + 4 \u00d7 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "39",
      "options": [
        "44",
        "37",
        "41",
        "39"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 4 + 3 \u00d7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "7",
      "options": [
        "9",
        "7",
        "5",
        "12"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 7 + 9 \u00d7 8?",
      "correctAnswer": "79",
      "options": [
        "77",
        "79",
        "81",
        "84"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 17 + 9 \u00d7 10?",
      "correctAnswer": "107",
      "options": [
        "109",
        "105",
        "107",
        "112"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 1 + 5 \u00d7 8?",
      "correctAnswer": "41",
      "options": [
        "46",
        "39",
        "43",
        "41"
      ]
    }
  ]
